them on.
Napoleon himself appearing in a black coat, rat-catcher breeches, and leather
leggings, while his favorite sow appeared in the watered silk dress which
Mrs. Jones had been used to wear on Sundays.
A week later, in the afternoon, a number of dog carts drove up to the farm.
A deputation of neighboring farmers had been invited to make a tour of inspection.
They were shown all over the farm and expressed great admiration for
everything they saw, especially the windmill.
The animals were weeding the turnip field.
They worked diligently, hardly raising their faces from the ground, and not
knowing whether to be more frightened of the pigs or of the human visitors.
That evening, loud laughter and bursts of singing came from the farmhouse.
And suddenly, at the sound of the mingled voices, the animals were stricken with curiosity.
What could be happening in there now that for the first time animals and
human beings were meeting on terms of equality?
With one accord, they began to creep as quietly as possible into the farmhouse garden.
At the gate, they paused, half frightened to go on, but Clover led the way in.
They tiptoed up to the house, and such animals as were tall enough peered in at
the dining room window.
There, round the long table, sat half a dozen farmers and half a dozen of the
more eminent pigs.
Napoleon himself occupying the seat of honor at the head of the table.
The pigs appeared completely at ease in their chairs.
The company had been enjoying a game of cards, but had broken off for the